* Courses
    
    Over 60 Languages

    View More
* Resources
    [
    
    Blog](https://ai.glossika.com/blog "glossika-blog")[
    
    Guides](https://ai.glossika.com/guides "glossika-guides")[
    
    Free Download](https://ai.glossika.com/free-download "glossika-free-download")
* English (US)
    [Français](https://ai.glossika.com/fra-SD/privacy "Français")[中文(台灣)](https://ai.glossika.com/zh-TW/privacy "中文(台灣)")[Pусский](https://ai.glossika.com/rus-SD/privacy "Pусский")

* Courses

Over 60 Languages

View More

* Resources

* English (US)

* [中文(台灣)](https://ai.glossika.com/zh-TW/privacy "中文(台灣)")

**Privacy Policy**
==================

Last updated: February 11, 2022

Welcome to Glossika (“Company,” “we,” “us,” or “our”). We are committed to protecting your personal information and your privacy. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to explain to you what information we collect, how we use it, and what rights you have in relation to it. Please read this carefully. If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or our practices with regard to your personal information, please contact us at [support@glossika.com](mailto:support@glossika.com)

The Privacy Policy describes how we might use your information if you:

* Visit our website at [ai.glossika.com](http://ai.glossika.com/)
* Download and use our mobile app(s) - Glossika
* Engage with us in other related ways including any sales, marketing, or events

**I. What information do we collect?**
======================================

**Personal information you disclose to us**
-------------------------------------------

We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us when you register on Glossika, express an interest in obtaining information about us or our products, and when you contact us.

The personal information that we collect depends on the context of your interactions with us, the choices you make and the products and features you use. The personal information we collect may include the following:

1. Your personal information: Your first name, last name, username, email address, shipping address and other similar information.
2. Payment data: We may collect data necessary to process your payment if you make purchases. All payments made on this site are processed by Stripe. You may find their privacy notice link here: [https://stripe.com/privacy](https://stripe.com/privacy)
3. Social media login data: We may provide you with the option to register with us using your existing social media account details, like your Facebook, Google or other social media account.

**Information automatically collected**
---------------------------------------

Some information such as your Internet Protocol address and/or browser and device information is collected automatically when you visit our Services.

We automatically collect certain information when you visit, use or navigate the Services. This information does not reveal your specific identity (like your name or contact information) but may include device and usage information, such as your IP address, browser and device information, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, device name, country, location, timezone, and other technical information. The information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operations of our Services, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes.

We also collect information through cookies and similar technologies.

The information we collect includes:

Log and Usage Data: It is service-related, diagnostic, usage and performance information our servers automatically collect when you access or use our Services and which we record in log files. Depending on how you interact with us, this log data may include your internet protocol (IP) address, device information, browser type and version, timezone setting and location, operating system, device event information (such as system activity, error reports).

**Information collected through our App**
-----------------------------------------

We collect information regarding your mobile device, push notifications when you use our App.

If you use our App, we also collect the following information:

Mobile device data: We automatically collect device information (such as your mobile device ID and model), operating system, version information and system configuration information, device and application identification numbers, browser type and version, hardware model, Internet service provider and/or mobile carrier, and Internet Protocol (IP) address (or proxy server). If you are using our App, we may also collect information about the phone network associated with your mobile device, your mobile device’s operating system or platform, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device’s unique ID and information about the feature of our App you accessed.

Push notifications: We may request to send you push notifications regarding your account or certain features of the App. If you wish to opt out from receiving these types of communications, you may turn them off in your device’s settings.

This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operating of our App, for troubleshooting and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes.

**Information collected from other sources**
--------------------------------------------

In order to enhance our ability to provide relevant marketing, offers and services to you and updated our records, we may obtain information about you from other sources, such as joint marketing partners, affiliate programs, data providers, social media platforms, and other third parties like Google Analytics, Mailchimp, and Intercom.

This information includes job titles, social media profiles, and custom profiles, for purposes of targeted advertising and event promotion. Any personal information that we collect from your social media account depends on your social media account’s privacy settings.

**II. How we use your information**
===================================

We process your information for purposes based on legitimate business interests, the fulfillment of our contract with you, compliance with our legal obligations, and/or your consent.

We use the information we collect or receive:

To facilitate account creation and the login process: If you choose to link your account with us to a third-party account (such as Google or Facebook account), we use the information you allowed to facilitate account creation and the login process.

Request feedback: We may use our information to request feedback and to contact you about your use of our Services.

To send information to you: We may use your personal information to send you product, service and new feature information and/or information about changes to our terms, conditions, and policies.

Fulfill and manage your subscriptions and orders: We may use your information to fulfill and manage your subscriptions, orders, payments, returns, and exchanges made through the Services.

To respond to inquiries/offer support to users: We may use your information to respond to your inquiries and solve issues you might have with the use of our Services.

To send you marketing and promotional communications: We and/or third-party marketing partners may use the personal information you send to us for our marketing purposes, if this is in accordance with your marketing preferences. You can opt out of our marketing emails at any time.

Deliver targeted advertising to you: We may use your information to develop and display personalized content and advertising (and work with third parties who do so) tailored to your interests and/or location and to measure its effectiveness.

**III. Will your information be shared with anyone?**
=====================================================

We only share information with your consent, to comply with laws, to provide you with services, to protect your rights, or to fulfill business obligations.

**IV. Do we use cookies and other tracking technologies?**
==========================================================

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to access or store information specifically related to your progress through our courses.

**V. How do we handle your social logins?**
===========================================

If you choose to register or log in to our services using a social media account, we may have access to certain information about you. Please note that we do not control, and are not responsible for, other uses of your personal information by your third-party social media provider.

**VI. How long do we keep your information?**
=============================================

We keep your information as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in the privacy notice unless otherwise required by law.

**VII. The right to erasure**
=============================

If you want to be erased and wish your account to be removed, you can easily reach us at [support@glossika.com](mailto:support@glossika.com) or Intercom real-time chat via the homepage. We delete all the information we keep about you, with the exception of anything required to comply with the law. Once you confirm that you want to delete your account, we’ll remove all the information we have about you from our systems. We’ll also remove your information from all our activity logs and data stored in third-party systems.

Glossika sorts natural languages by structure and difficulty, delivering memory, pronunciation and fluency skills to language learners between any two languages.

Product

Courses [Pricing](https://ai.glossika.com/pricing "pricing") [Stories](https://ai.glossika.com/stories "user stories") [Organizations](https://ai.glossika.com/organization "Organizations") [Viva](https://viva.glossika.com/ "Viva")

Resources

Company

Recent Posts

[Opera Singer to Polyglot: "No character opens their mouth to speak unless they want something"](https://ai.glossika.com/blog/opera-singer-to-polyglot-no-character-opens-their-mouth-to-speak-unless-they-want-something "blog") [Language fossilization: What it is and how to overcome it](https://ai.glossika.com/blog/language-fossilization "blog") [The Future of Taiwanese Hokkien in a Mandarin-Dominant Taiwan](https://ai.glossika.com/blog/the-future-of-taiwanese-hokkien-in-a-mandarin-dominant-taiwan "blog") [Read More →](https://ai.glossika.com/blog "blog")

Get the latest news and updates!

 Subscribe

Subscribed!

© 2024, Glossika.com. All rights reserved.  
[Privacy](https://ai.glossika.com/privacy "privacy") and [Terms](https://ai.glossika.com/terms "terms")

Cookies Policy
--------------

We use cookies to offer better user experience. Cookies enable you to enjoy certain features like getting personalized language learning content. By using Glossika, you accept our [use of cookies.](https://ai.glossika.com/zh-TW/terms)

AGREE

* * *

Android user? [](http://eepurl.com/byXG4v)to be the first to know when our Android app is released.

Glossika

Learn on the go
